mindzinger.com 2008-12-01

# MindZinger :: Free Homework Help :: Privacy

_(revised August 8th, 2007)_

####  What This Privacy Policy Covers

  * This policy covers how MindZinger treats personal information that MindZinger collects and receives, including information related to your past use of MindZinger services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that MindZinger does not own or control, or to people that MindZinger does not employ or manage. 

####  Information Collection and Use 

_General_

  * MindZinger collects personal information when you register with MindZinger, when you use MindZinger services, when you visit MindZinger pages or the pages of certain MindZinger partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. MindZinger may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, and ZIP or postal code. When you register with MindZinger and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * MindZinger collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. 
  * MindZinger automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, MindZinger cookie information, and the page you request. 
  * MindZinger uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

####  Information Sharing and Disclosure 

  * MindZinger does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with MindZinger under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help MindZinger communicate with you about offers from MindZinger and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MindZinger's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if MindZinger is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, MindZinger will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * MindZinger displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 
    * MindZinger does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 

####  Cookies 

  * MindZinger may set and access MindZinger cookies on your computer. 
  * MindZinger lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to MindZinger's cookies. 

####  Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences 

_General_

  * You can edit your MindZinger account information at any time.  To deactivate your account, please send an email to support@mindzinger.com with this request.  Note that per the MindZinger Terms of Use, all users of the MindZinger website grant a license to MindZinger for the continual use of the content posted to the website. 
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the MindZinger service, such as service announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of your MindZinger account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

####  Confidentiality and Security 

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy 

  * MindZinger may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your MindZinger account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

Questions and Suggestions 

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please complete the feedback form found after clicking the "support" link at the bottom of any MindZinger webpage.
